<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hack De Wereld on HackDeWereld</title>
    <link>https://hackdewereld.nl/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hack De Wereld on HackDeWereld</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 18:27:58 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hackdewereld.nl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>0x08 Binary Exploitation</title>
      <link>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/0x08-binary-exploitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 22:29:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/0x08-binary-exploitation/</guid>
      <description>This meetup was all about binary exploitation. Our community member Alexandru took us through Assembly, Shell Code and Buffer overflows. We looked at the basics of assemblies, the registers that you will commonly find and how a C program translates to assembly.
After the presentation we had a small quiz. Just to do something different then listening to technical talks and to determine who should get some prizes. In the end we were able to give away 3 VIP passes and a 1 month Pro Labs subscription.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0x07 A CTF</title>
      <link>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/0x07-ctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 22:26:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/0x07-ctf/</guid>
      <description>The 7th meetup is a wrap. This entire meetup was focused on a single thing: a CTF. Our community member @danielyc had created a cool CTF for his dayjob and they were willing to share it with us!
This meetup things were different. Instead of Zoom we used discord and youtube to connect with people. We already use discord extensively for our community during meetups. When using Zoom all the coordination falls to a single person; the organizer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0x06 Threat Hunting with Milad</title>
      <link>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/0x06-threat-hunting-with-milad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 09:45:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/0x06-threat-hunting-with-milad/</guid>
      <description>We are halfway through our first year of existance! During the pandemic we have started a meetup and have been growing bigger every edition! At this point the meetup brings together about 50 people from over the dutch (and international) industry and enthousiasts that want to get started with hacking.
Stuff goes wrong Sometimes stuff just goes wrong. Last meetup the emails from meetup.com were blank when I mailed out the passwords to the meetup and this week it seems a number of guests did not receive the email or it was delivered to their spam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0x05 HTB Content Creation</title>
      <link>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/0x05-htb-content-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 16:24:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/0x05-htb-content-creation/</guid>
      <description>Vacation time is over, but we are still all at home due to the Corona Virus. This does not stop us from having yet another great meetup! 45 people gathered to listen to a great talk / Q&amp;amp;A and competed in a game of trivia with amazing prizes. The night was closed out with the traditional reading of a Miffy story.
Ian Austin / egre55   Ian talked to us about the thoughts behind content development at Hack The Box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0x04 CVE hunting, Queries and Miffy</title>
      <link>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/0x04-cve-queries-miffy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 23:10:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/0x04-cve-queries-miffy/</guid>
      <description>The July meetup is a wrap! Our 4th corona time online meetup was another great success. We had 45 participants showing up to listen to a great talk about CVE hunting, hacking along with one of the medium difficulty machines and finishing off with the reading of Miffy at the Zoo.
CVE Hunting Melvin gave his first public presentation today. He just finished his OSWE certification and in the process found a CVE in an open source project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://hackdewereld.nl/codeofconduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackdewereld.nl/codeofconduct/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Diversity and inclusion make our community strong. We encourage participation from the most varied and diverse backgrounds possible and want to be very clear about where we stand.
Our goal is to maintain a safe, helpful and friendly community for everyone.
This code and related procedures also apply to unacceptable behaviour occurring outside the scope of community activities, in all community venues— online and in-person— as well as in all one-on-one communications, and anywhere such behaviour has the potential to adversely affect the safety or well-being of community members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moderation Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://hackdewereld.nl/modguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackdewereld.nl/modguide/</guid>
      <description>Introduction It is important that all users’ questions, answers and comments are in line with the Hack de Wereld Discord Code of Conduct, as well as with the category and topic, or channel, they belong to. When deciding to approach a user, moderators and administrators must always assume intentions are good, which is usually the case. Over-moderation is harmful to the atmosphere of the community and should be avoided.
Expectations for moderator enforcement While in practice most actions from moderators and administrators will be friendly reminders, they should act on complaints/reports quickly and involve other team members if necessary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0x03 And we start our journey</title>
      <link>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/0x03-we-start-our-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 22:43:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/0x03-we-start-our-journey/</guid>
      <description>The June meetup is a wrap! Our community is growing and we are getting to know each other quite well. A very cool thing to see is that the same people keep showing up, most have been around since the 1st meetup back in April!
The meetup started off with a presentation by Leandro (ceso). After passing his OSCP certification last month I asked him to share some of his thoughts on what you should do to get started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0x02 Just Enough Reverse Engineering</title>
      <link>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/just-enough-reverse-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 11:01:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/just-enough-reverse-engineering/</guid>
      <description>We had our 2nd meetup last night. Again a large group of Hack The Box friends showed up and we had a great time! We hit a milestone just before the meeting with a whopping 300 members in our Hack The Box NL group on meetup.com.
The theme for the meetup was Reverse Engineering. There was a presentation by Arjen on getting started with the reverse engineering challenges on Hack The Box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The first Wednesday Hackday meetup</title>
      <link>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/first-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 10:25:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/first-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last night we had our first official Wednesday Hackday meetup. It was a great success with 25 people showing up to learn about Hack The Box and hacking in general. The meetup was Virtual due to the Corona Measures in place across the country.
The meetup started with some introductions and a getting started message by Sotiria from Hack The Box. It is great to be part of the Hack The Box family of meetups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://hackdewereld.nl/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackdewereld.nl/about/</guid>
      <description>We are a community of Dutch cyber security professionals and enthusiasts that get together once per month to hack boxes and discuss hacking techniques. We are based in The Netherlands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hackdewereld.nl/discord/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackdewereld.nl/discord/</guid>
      <description>Discord We have agreat community over on our discord channel. Feel free to drop in and join the discussion!
   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
