<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on HackDeWereld</title>
    <link>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on HackDeWereld</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 16:24:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>0x05 HTB Content Creation</title>
      <link>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/0x05-htb-content-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 16:24:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/0x05-htb-content-creation/</guid>
      <description>Vacation time is over, but we are still all at home due to the Corona Virus. This does not stop us from having yet another great meetup! 45 people gathered to listen to a great talk / Q&amp;amp;A and competed in a game of trivia with amazing prizes. The night was closed out with the traditional reading of a Miffy story.
Ian Austin / egre55   Ian talked to us about the thoughts behind content development at Hack The Box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0x04 CVE hunting, Queries and Miffy</title>
      <link>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/0x04-cve-queries-miffy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 23:10:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/0x04-cve-queries-miffy/</guid>
      <description>The July meetup is a wrap! Our 4th corona time online meetup was another great success. We had 45 participants showing up to listen to a great talk about CVE hunting, hacking along with one of the medium difficulty machines and finishing off with the reading of Miffy at the Zoo.
CVE Hunting Melvin gave his first public presentation today. He just finished his OSWE certification and in the process found a CVE in an open source project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0x03 And we start our journey</title>
      <link>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/0x03-we-start-our-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 22:43:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/0x03-we-start-our-journey/</guid>
      <description>The June meetup is a wrap! Our community is growing and we are getting to know each other quite well. A very cool thing to see is that the same people keep showing up, most have been around since the 1st meetup back in April!
The meetup started off with a presentation by Leandro (ceso). After passing his OSCP certification last month I asked him to share some of his thoughts on what you should do to get started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0x02 Just Enough Reverse Engineering</title>
      <link>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/just-enough-reverse-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 11:01:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/just-enough-reverse-engineering/</guid>
      <description>We had our 2nd meetup last night. Again a large group of Hack The Box friends showed up and we had a great time! We hit a milestone just before the meeting with a whopping 300 members in our Hack The Box NL group on meetup.com.
The theme for the meetup was Reverse Engineering. There was a presentation by Arjen on getting started with the reverse engineering challenges on Hack The Box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The first Wednesday Hackday meetup</title>
      <link>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/first-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 10:25:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackdewereld.nl/posts/first-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last night we had our first official Wednesday Hackday meetup. It was a great success with 25 people showing up to learn about Hack The Box and hacking in general. The meetup was Virtual due to the Corona Measures in place across the country.
The meetup started with some introductions and a getting started message by Sotiria from Hack The Box. It is great to be part of the Hack The Box family of meetups.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
